lawyercentral.com 2019-08-16

# Privacy Notice

###  Information We Collect 

Generally, you control the amount and type of information that you provide to us when using our website.

**What Happens If You Don't Give Us Your PD?**

If you do not provide us with enough PD, we may not be able to provide you with all our services. However, you can access and use some parts of our website without giving us your PD.

**We Collect Your PD in the Following Ways:**

  * **Automatic Information**   
We automatically receive information from your web browser or mobile device. This information includes the name of the website from which you entered our website, if any, as well as the name of the website you'll visit when you leave our website. This information also includes the IP address of your computer/the proxy server you use to access the Internet, your Internet service provider's name, your web browser type, the type of mobile device, your computer operating system, and data about your browsing activity when using our website. We use all this information to analyze trends among our users to help improve our website.
  * **When Entering and Using Our Website**   
When you enter and use our website and agree to accept cookies, some of these cookies may contain your PD. 
  * **When You Sign Up for Our Newsletter**   
When you sign up for our newsletter to receive information about new cases, investigations, settlement deadlines, and information about our services, we collect your name and email address. 
  * **When You Report a Potential Claim**   
When you report a potential claim, we collect your first name, last name, IP address, email address, phone number, zip code, and your case details. 
  * **Website Chat Software**   
Our website contains chat software that enable visitors to communicate with us live online or offline by email. In some cases, visitors can communicate with us without becoming a member or buying our services. When you use this chat software, we may collect some or all the following information: your email address, first name, last name, location, and any other information you willingly choose to provide to us. You should limit the information you provide to us that is only necessary to answer your questions. 

###  Our Use of Cookies 

Our website uses cookies. A cookie is a small piece of data or a text file that is downloaded to your computer or mobile device when you access certain websites. Cookies may contain text that can be read by the web server that delivered the cookie to you. The text contained in the cookie generally consists of a sequence of letters and numbers that uniquely identifies your computer or mobile device; it may contain other information as well. 

**By agreeing to accept our use of cookies, you are giving us, and third parties we partner with, permission to place, store, and access some or all the cookies described below on your computer.**

  * _Strictly Necessary Cookies_   
These cookies are necessary for proper functioning of the website, such as displaying content, logging in, validating your session, responding to your request for services, and other functions. Most web browsers can be set to disable the use of cookies. However, if you disable these cookies, you may not be able to access features on our website correctly or at all. 
  * _Performance Cookies_   
These cookies collect information about the use of the website, such as pages visited, traffic sources, users' interests, content management, and other website measurements. 
  * _Functional Cookies_   
These cookies enable the website to remember a user's choices - such as their language, user name, and other personal choices - while using the website. They can also be used to deliver services, such as letting a user make a blog post, listen to audio, or watch videos on the website.
  * _Media Cookies_   
These cookies can be used to improve a website's performance and provide special features and content. They can be placed by third parties who provide services to us or by our company. 
  * _Advertising or Targeting Cookies_   
These cookies are usually placed and used by advertising companies to develop a profile of your browsing interests and serve advertisements on other websites that are related to your interests. You will see less advertising if you disable these cookies.
  * _Session Cookies_   
These cookies allow websites to link the actions of a user during a browser session. They may be used for a variety of purposes, such as remembering what a user has put in their shopping cart as they browse a website. Session cookies also permit users to be recognized as they navigate a website so that any item or page changes they make are remembered from page to page. Session cookies expire after a browser session; thus, they are not stored long term.
  * _Persistent Cookies_   
These cookies are stored on a user's device in between browser sessions, which allows the user's preferences or actions across a site (or, in some cases, across different sites) to be remembered. Persistent cookies may be used for a variety of purposes, including remembering users' choices and preferences when using a website or to target advertising to them. 

We may also use cookies for:

  * Identifying the areas of our website that you have visited
  * Personalizing content that you see on our website
  * Our website analytics
  * Remarketing our services to you
  * Remembering your preferences, settings, and login details
  * Targeted advertising and serving ads relevant to your interests
  * Allowing you to post comments
  * Allowing you to share content with social networks

Most web browsers can be set to disable the use of cookies. However, if you disable cookies, you may not be able to access features on our website correctly or at all. 

**Web Beacons**   
We may also use a technology called web beacons to collect general information about your use of our website and your use of special promotions or newsletters. The information we collect by web beacons allows us to statistically monitor the number of people who open our emails. Web beacons also help us to understand the behavior of our customers, members, and visitors. 

**Google Ad and Content Network Privacy Notice**   
Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's past visits to our website. Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visits to our site and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>

**Google Analytics Privacy Notice**   
Our website uses Google Analytics to collect information about the use of our website. Google Analytics collects information from users such as age, gender, interests, demographics, how often they visit our website, what pages they visit, and what other websites they have used before coming to our website. We use the information we get from Google Analytics to analyze traffic, remarket our services to users, improve our marketing, advertising, and to improve our website. We have enabled Google Analytics advertising features such as remarketing with Google Analytics, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit our website, not your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected using Google Analytics with PD. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit our website, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google also uses specific identifiers to help collect information about the use of our website. For more information on how Google collects and processes your data, visit <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/>

You can prevent Google Analytics from using your information by opting out at this link: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>

**Google Remarketing**   
Why am I seeing ads by Google for products and services I've viewed?   
Our website uses a remarketing advertising service. Our remarketing service is provided by Google and other companies that show our ads on websites across the Internet. With remarketing you may see ads for our services you have previously looked at. As an example, suppose you visit a website that sells computers, but you do not buy a computer on your first visit to that website. The website's owner might like to encourage you to revisit his/her site and buy a computer by showing you his/her ads again on other websites that you visit. We use remarketing for similar purposes. For this to happen, Google will read a cookie that is already in your browser, or they place a cookie in your browser when you visit our site or other sites using remarketing. You can opt out of Google's use of cookies and remarketing at this link: <https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en> or you can opt out using the Network Advertising Initiative opt out page at: <http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#!/>

**Facebook Remarketing**   
Third parties, including Facebook, may use cookies, web beacons, and other storage technologies to collect or receive information from our website and elsewhere on the internet, and use that information to provide measurement services and target ads. With Facebook remarketing you may see our ads on Facebook after you have visited our site. For this to happen, Facebook uses a Custom Audience Pixel that is activated when a visitor lands on a webpage and a unique "cookie" is placed in their browser. Facebook lookalike audience targeting allows us to show ads on Facebook to people who are similar to those who have already visited or made a purchase from our website. To opt out of Facebook's collection and use of information for ad targeting visit: <https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217>

**Remarketing**   
Our website and applications use remarketing advertising services other than Google and Facebook. These remarketing services are provided by companies that show our ads on websites and devices across the Internet. With remarketing you may see ads for our products you have previously looked at. For this to happen remarketing companies will read a cookie in your browser. This can only happen if your browser is set to let it happen. You can opt out of these types of advertising cookies by visiting <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>

**Hotjar Disclosure**   
We use [www.Hotjar.com](http://www.hotjar.com/) in order to better understand our users' needs and to optimize this service and experience. Hotjar is a technology service that helps us better understand our users experience like how much time they spend on which pages, which links they choose to click, what users do and don't like, etc.) and this enables us to build and maintain our service with user feedback. Hotjar uses cookies and other technologies to collect data on our users' behavior and their devices (in particular device's IP address (captured and stored only in anonymized form), device screen size, device type (unique device identifiers), browser information, geographic location (country only), preferred language used to display our website). Hotjar stores this information in a pseudonymized user profile. Neither Hotjar nor we use this information to identify individual users or to match it with further data on an individual user. For further details, please see Hotjar's privacy policy by visiting: <https://www.hotjar.com/legal/policies/privacy>

You can opt-out to the creation of a user profile, Hotjar's storing of data about your usage of our website and Hotjar's use of tracking cookies on other websites by following this by visiting <https://www.hotjar.com/legal/compliance/opt-out>

**Disqus Disclosure**   
Disqus.com is a service that can track users' activity across different websites that use the Disqus commenting system unless a "do not track" option is enabled. Information tracked by Disqus may be disclosed to third parties including pseudonymous analytics data, web browser version, installed add-ons, referring pages, and exit links. Other users may search for, see, use, and repost any of your user content that you make publicly available through the service. You can choose to install a privacy-enhancing web browser extension which allows some of Disqus to be blocked. 

###  How Your Information Is Used 

We use the information we receive from you to:

  * Provide our services you have requested or purchased from us
  * Personalize and customize our content
  * Make improvements to our website
  * Contact you with updates to our website
  * Resolve problems and disputes
  * Contact you with marketing and advertising that we believe may be of interest to you

**Communications and Emails**   
When we communicate with you about our website, we will use the email address you provided when you registered as a member or user. 

**Sharing Information With Affiliates and Other Third Parties**   
We do not sell or rent your PD to third parties for marketing purposes. We may provide your PD to third-party service providers we hire to provide services to us. These third-party service providers may include but are not limited to: payment processors, web analytics companies, advertising networks, call centers, data management services, help desk providers, accountants, law firms, auditors, shopping cart and email service providers, and shipping companies. 

**Sharing Information With Facebook and Google for Marketing Purposes**   
We may share your PD with third parties for similar audience marketing purposes. Similar audience marketing is also called lookalike audience marketing. The third parties we share your PD with for this type of marketing include Facebook and/or Google. Using your PD, for similar audience marketing or lookalike audience marketing helps us find new audiences (users and customers) based on similar interests to yours, this helps us improve our marketing services. Your PD is only shared with Facebook and Google for this type of marketing. By using our website and agreeing to our privacy notice, you are giving your consent for your PD to be used for the marketing purposes described within this section. 

**Sharing Information With Attorneys**   
When you submit a report for a claim or file for a claim, your information and inquiry will be forwarded to one of the attorneys we work with. 

**Legally Required Releases of Information**   
We may be legally required to disclose your PD if such disclosure is (a) required by subpoena, law, or other legal process; (b) necessary to assist law enforcement officials or government enforcement agencies; (c) necessary to investigate violations of or otherwise enforce our Legal Terms; (d) necessary to protect us from legal action or claims from third parties, including you and/or other users or members; or (e) necessary to protect the legal rights, personal/real property, or personal safety of our company, users, employees, and affiliates. 

**Disclosures to Successors**   
If our business is sold or merges in whole or in part with another business that would become responsible for providing the website to you, we retain the right to transfer your PD to the new business. The new business would retain the right to use your PD according to the terms of this privacy notice as well as to any changes to this privacy notice as instituted by the new business. 

We also retain the right to transfer your PD if our company files for bankruptcy and some or all of our assets are sold to another individual or business. 

**Community Discussion Boards**   
Our website may offer the ability for users to communicate with each other through online community discussion boards or other mechanisms. We do not filter or monitor what is posted on such discussion boards. If you choose to post on these discussion boards, you should use care when exposing any PD, as such information is not protected by our privacy notice nor are we liable if you choose to disclose your PD through such postings. Also, PD you post on our website for publication may be available worldwide by means of the Internet. We cannot prevent the use or misuse of such information by others. 

###  Retaining and Destroying Your PD 

We retain information that we collect from you (including your PD) only for as long as we need it for legal, business, or tax purposes. Your information may be retained in electronic form, paper form, or a combination of both. When your information is no longer needed, we will destroy, delete, or erase it. 

###  Protecting the Privacy Rights of Third Parties 

If any postings you make on our website contain information about third parties, you must make sure you have permission to include that information in your posting. While we are not legally liable for the actions of our users, we will remove any postings about which we are notified, if such postings violate the privacy rights of others. 

###  Do Not Track Settings 

Some web browsers have settings that enable you to request that our website not track your movement within our website. Our website does not obey such settings when transmitted to and detected by our website. You can turn off tracking features and other security settings in your browser by referring to your browser's user manual. 

###  Links to Other Websites 

Our website may contain links to other websites. These websites are not under our control and are not subject to our privacy notice. These websites will likely have their own privacy notices. We have no responsibility for these websites and we provide links to these websites solely for your convenience. You acknowledge that your use of and access to these websites are solely at your risk. It is your responsibility to check the privacy notices of these websites to see how they treat your PD. 

###  Protecting Children's Privacy 

Even though our website is not designed for use by anyone under the age of 18, we realize that a child under the age of 16 may attempt to access our website. We do not knowingly collect PD from children under the age of 16. If you are a parent or guardian and believe that your child is using our website, please contact us. Before we remove any information, we may ask for proof of identification to prevent malicious removal of account information. If we discover that a child is accessing our website, we will delete his/her information within a reasonable period of time. You acknowledge that we do not verify the age of our users nor do we have any liability to do so. 

###  Our Email Policy 

You can always opt out of receiving further email correspondence from us or our affiliates. We will not sell, rent, or trade your email address to any unaffiliated third party without your permission except in the sale or transfer of our business, or if our company files for bankruptcy. 

###  Our Security Policy 

We have built our website using industry-standard security measures and authentication tools to protect the security of your PD. We and the third parties who provide services for us, also maintain technical and physical safeguards to protect your PD. When we collect your credit card information through our website, we will encrypt it before it travels over the Internet using industry-standard technology for conducting secure online transactions. Unfortunately, we cannot guarantee against the loss or misuse of your PD or secure data transmission over the Internet because of its nature. 

We strongly urge you to protect any password you may have for our website and to not share it with anyone. You should always log out of our website when you finish using it, especially if you are sharing or using a computer in a public place. 

###  Use of Your Credit Card 

You may have to provide a credit card to buy services from our website. We use third-party billing services and have no control over these services. We use our commercially reasonable efforts to make sure your credit card number is kept strictly confidential by using only third-party billing services that use industry-standard encryption technology to protect your credit card number from unauthorized use. However, you understand and agree that we are in no way responsible for any misuse of your credit card number. 

###  Changes to Our Privacy Notice 

We reserve the right to change this privacy notice at any time. If our company decides to change this privacy notice, we will post those changes on our website so that our users and customers are always aware of what information we collect, use, and disclose. If at any time we decide to disclose or use your PD in a method different from that specified at the time it was collected, we will provide advance notice by email (sent to the email address on file in your account). Otherwise we will use and disclose our users' and customers' PD in agreement with the privacy notice in effect when the information was collected. In all cases, your continued use of our website and services after any change to this privacy notice will constitute your acceptance of such change. 

###  Questions About Our Privacy Notice 

If you have any questions about our privacy notice, please contact us using the information at the top of this privacy notice.
